I think it's just a relative. I need a healing potion!
Can't you sell me anything?
Oh, here we go.
There we go.
25?
Sweet!
I got this money from...
I got this money from your husband at the tavern.
Alright, let's go take this to, uh, what's his name? Oh, here's his place, let's see if I can find him. Can I climb this?
Let's try another spot.
Oh, we can also try stealing lots of people.
It's late at night.
Why not?
Practice the trade. That guy's...
He can wait until morning. Probably can't.
Probably not.
What's our thieving at right now?
And 10, 14, favoring 26.
I'm assuming out of 100, that's not too bad.
In the name of justice, it's unfortunate.
Spend your life in jail.
Are there any tools or anything?